[
  {
    "id": "01",
    "question": "Which of the following keywords is used to define a variable in Javascript?",
    "options": [
      "var",
      "let",
      "Both A and B",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "Both A and B"
  },
  {
    "id": "02",
    "question": "Which of the following methods is used to access HTML elements using Javascript?",
    "options": ["getElementbyId()", "getElementsByClassName()", "Both A and B", "None of the above"],
    "answer": "Both A and B"
  },
  {
    "id": "03",
    "question": "Which of the following methods can be used to display data in some form using Javascript?",
    "options": ["document.write()", "console.log()", "window.alert()", "All of the above"],
    "answer": "All of the above"
  },
  {
    "id": "04",
    "question": "How can a datatype be declared to be a constant type?",
    "options": ["const", "var", "let", "constant"],
    "answer": "const"
  },
  {
    "id": "05",
    "question": "Which of the following are closures in Javascript?",
    "options": ["Variables", "Functions", "Objects", "All of the above"],
    "answer": "All of the above"
  },
  {
    "id": "06",
    "question": "How to stop an interval timer in Javascript?",
    "options": [
      "clearInterval",
      "clearTime",
      "intervalOver",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "clearInterval"
  },
  {
    "id": "07",
    "question": "How do we write a comment in javascript?",
    "options": [
      "/**/",
      "//",
      "#",
      "$$"
    ],
    "answer": "//"
  },
  {
    "id": "08",
    "question": "Which of the following are not server-side Javascript objects?",
    "options": [
      "Date",
      "FileUpload",
      "Function",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "All of the above"
  },
  {
    "id": "09",
    "question": "Which function is used to serialize an object into a JSON string in Javascript?",
    "options": ["stringify()", "parse()", "convert()", "None of the above"],
    "answer": "stringify()"
  },
  {
    "id": "10",
    "question": "What keyword is used to declare an asynchronous function in Javascript?",
    "options": ["async", "await", "setTimeout", "text-position"],
    "answer": "async"
  }
]
